{
    "PubmedBookArticle": [],
    "PubmedArticle": [
        {
            "MedlineCitation": {
                "OtherAbstract": [],
                "GeneralNote": [],
                "OtherID": [],
                "SpaceFlightMission": [],
                "KeywordList": [],
                "CitationSubset": [
                    "IM"
                ],
                "PMID": "11007896",
                "DateCompleted": {
                    "Year": "2001",
                    "Month": "02",
                    "Day": "22"
                },
                "DateRevised": {
                    "Year": "2023",
                    "Month": "11",
                    "Day": "20"
                },
                "Article": {
                    "ELocationID": [],
                    "Language": [
                        "eng"
                    ],
                    "ArticleDate": [],
                    "Journal": {
                        "ISSN": "1529-2401",
                        "JournalIssue": {
                            "Volume": "20",
                            "Issue": "19",
                            "PubDate": {
                                "Year": "2000",
                                "Month": "Oct",
                                "Day": "01"
                            }
                        },
                        "Title": "The Journal of neuroscience : the official journal of the Society for Neuroscience",
                        "ISOAbbreviation": "J Neurosci"
                    },
                    "ArticleTitle": "Enhanced proliferation, survival, and dopaminergic differentiation of CNS precursors in lowered oxygen.",
                    "Pagination": {
                        "StartPage": "7377",
                        "EndPage": "7383",
                        "MedlinePgn": "7377-83"
                    },
                    "Abstract": {
                        "AbstractText": [
                            "Standard cell culture systems impose environmental oxygen (O(2)) levels of 20%, whereas actual tissue O(2) levels in both developing and adult brain are an order of magnitude lower. To address whether proliferation and differentiation of CNS precursors in vitro are influenced by the O(2) environment, we analyzed embryonic day 12 rat mesencephalic precursor cells in traditional cultures with 20% O(2) and in lowered O(2) (3 +/- 2%). Proliferation was promoted and apoptosis was reduced when cells were grown in lowered O(2), yielding greater numbers of precursors. The differentiation of precursor cells into neurons with specific neurotransmitter phenotypes was also significantly altered. The percentage of neurons of dopaminergic phenotype increased to 56% in lowered O(2) compared with 18% in 20% O(2). Together, the increases in total cell number and percentage of dopaminergic neurons resulted in a ninefold net increase in dopamine neuron yield. Differential gene expression analysis revealed more abundant messages for FGF8, engrailed-1, and erythropoietin in lowered O(2). Erythropoietin supplementation of 20% O(2) cultures partially mimicked increased dopaminergic differentiation characteristic of CNS precursors cultured in lowered O(2). These data demonstrate increased proliferation, reduced cell death, and enhanced dopamine neuron generation in lowered O(2), making this method an important advance in the ex vivo generation of specific neurons for brain repair."
                        ]
                    },
                    "AuthorList": [
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [
                                {
                                    "Identifier": [],
                                    "Affiliation": "Laboratory of Molecular Biology, National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Stroke, National Institutes of Health, Bethesda, Maryland 20892, USA."
                                }
                            ],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "Studer",
                            "ForeName": "L",
                            "Initials": "L"
                        },
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "Csete",
                            "ForeName": "M",
                            "Initials": "M"
                        },
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "Lee",
                            "ForeName": "S H",
                            "Initials": "SH"
                        },
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "Kabbani",
                            "ForeName": "N",
                            "Initials": "N"
                        },
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "Walikonis",
                            "ForeName": "J",
                            "Initials": "J"
                        },
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "Wold",
                            "ForeName": "B",
                            "Initials": "B"
                        },
                        {
                            "AffiliationInfo": [],
                            "Identifier": [],
                            "LastName": "McKay",
                            "ForeName": "R",
                            "Initials": "R"
                        }
                    ],
                    "GrantList": [
                        {
                            "GrantID": "AR40780-8",
                            "Acronym": "AR",
                            "Agency": "NIAMS NIH HHS",
                            "Country": "United States"
                        },
                        {
                            "GrantID": "AR42671-05",
                            "Acronym": "AR",
                            "Agency": "NIAMS NIH HHS",
                            "Country": "United States"
                        }
                    ],
                    "PublicationTypeList": [
                        "Journal Article",
                        "Research Support, U.S. Gov't, Non-P.H.S.",
                        "Research Support, U.S. Gov't, P.H.S."
                    ]
                },
                "MedlineJournalInfo": {
                    "Country": "United States",
                    "MedlineTA": "J Neurosci",
                    "NlmUniqueID": "8102140",
                    "ISSNLinking": "0270-6474"
                },
                "ChemicalList": [
                    {
                        "RegistryNumber": "0",
                        "NameOfSubstance": "Antigens, Differentiation"
                    },
                    {
                        "RegistryNumber": "103107-01-3",
                        "NameOfSubstance": "Fibroblast Growth Factor 2"
                    },
                    {
                        "RegistryNumber": "11096-26-7",
                        "NameOfSubstance": "Erythropoietin"
                    },
                    {
                        "RegistryNumber": "G34N38R2N1",
                        "NameOfSubstance": "Bromodeoxyuridine"
                    },
                    {
                        "RegistryNumber": "S88TT14065",
                        "NameOfSubstance": "Oxygen"
                    },
                    {
                        "RegistryNumber": "VTD58H1Z2X",
                        "NameOfSubstance": "Dopamine"
                    }
                ],
                "MeshHeadingList": [
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [],
                        "DescriptorName": "Animals"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "metabolism"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Antigens, Differentiation"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "drug effects",
                            "physiology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Apoptosis"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [],
                        "DescriptorName": "Bromodeoxyuridine"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "drug effects",
                            "physiology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Cell Differentiation"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "drug effects",
                            "physiology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Cell Division"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "physiology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Cell Hypoxia"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "physiology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Cell Lineage"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "drug effects",
                            "physiology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Cell Survival"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "cytology",
                            "drug effects",
                            "metabolism"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Central Nervous System"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "metabolism"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Dopamine"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "metabolism",
                            "pharmacology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Erythropoietin"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "metabolism",
                            "pharmacology"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Fibroblast Growth Factor 2"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [],
                        "DescriptorName": "In Situ Nick-End Labeling"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "metabolism"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Oxygen"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [],
                        "DescriptorName": "Rats"
                    },
                    {
                        "QualifierName": [
                            "cytology",
                            "drug effects",
                            "metabolism"
                        ],
                        "DescriptorName": "Stem Cells"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "PubmedData": {
                "ReferenceList": [
                    {
                        "ReferenceList": [],
                        "Reference": [
                            {
                                "Citation": "Bany-Mohammed FM, Slivka S, Hallman M. Recombinant human erythropoietin: possible role as an antioxidant in premature rabbits. Pediatr Res. 1996;40:381\u2013387.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "8865272"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Colton DA, Pagan F, Snell J, Colton JS, Cummins A, Gilbert DL. Protection from oxidation enhances the survival of cultured mesencephalic neurons. Exp Neurol. 1995;132:54\u201361.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7720826"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Czyzyk-Krzeska MF, Furnari BA, Lawson EE, Millhorn DE. Hypoxia increases rate of transcription and stability of tyrosine hydroxylase mRNA in pheochromocytoma (PC12) cells. J Biol Chem. 1994;269:760\u2013764.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7903970"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Danelian PS, McMahon AP. Engrailed-1 as a target of the Wnt-1 signalling pathway in vertebrate midbrain development. Nature. 1996;383:332\u2013334.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "8848044"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Echelard Y, Epstein DJ, St-Jacques B, Shen L, Mahler J, McMahon JA, McMahon AP. Sonic hedgehog, a member of a family of putative signaling molecules, is implicated in the regulation of CNS polarity. Cell. 1993;75:1417\u20131430.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7916661"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Ericson J, Muhr J, Placzek M, Lints T, Jessell TM, Edlund T. Sonic hedgehog induces the differentiation of ventral forebrain neurons: a common signal for ventral patterning within the neural tube. Cell. 1995;81:747\u2013756.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7774016"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Freeman TB, Vawter DE, Leaverton PE, Godbold JH, Hauser RA, Goetz CG, Olanow CW. Use of placebo surgery in controlled trials of a cellular-based therapy for Parkinson's disease. N Engl J Med. 2000;341:988\u2013992.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10498497"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Gemel J, Jacobsen C, MacArthur CA. Fibroblast growth factor-8 expression is regulated by intronic engrailed and Pbx1-binding sites. J Biol Chem. 1999;274:6020\u20136026.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10026229"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Goda F, O'Hara JA, Liu KJ, Rhodes ES, Dunn JF, Swartz HJ. Comparisons of measurements of pO2 in tissue in vivo by EPR oximetry and microelectrodes. Adv Exp Med Biol. 1997;411:543\u2013549.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9269471"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Gross J, Ungethum U, Andreeva N, Heldt J, Gao J, Marschhausen G, Altmann T, Muller I, Husemann B, Andersson K. Hypoxia during early developmental period induces long-term changes in the dopamine content and release in a mesencephalic cell culture. Neuroscience. 1999;92:699\u2013704.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10408618"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Gundersen HJG, Bendtsen TF, Korbo L, Marcussen N, Moller A, Nielsen K, Nyengaard JR, Pakkenberg B, Soerensen FB, Vesterby A, West MJ. Some new, simple and efficient stereological methods and their use in pathological research and diagnosis. APMIS. 1988;96:379\u2013394.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "3288247"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Guyton AC, Hall JE. Textbook of medical physiology. Saunders; Philadelphia: 1996."
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Hynes M, Rosenthal A. Specification of dopaminergic and serotonergic neurons in the vertebrate CNS. Curr Opin Neurobiol. 1999;9:26\u201336.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10072377"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Hynes M, Poulsen K, Tessier-Lavigne M, Rosenthal A. Control of neuronal diversity by the floor plate: contact-mediated induction of midbrain dopaminergic neurons. Cell. 1995;80:95\u2013101.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7813022"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Johe KK, Hazel TG, Muller T, Dugich-Djordjevic MM, McKay RD. Single factors direct the differentiation of stem cells from the fetal and adult central nervous system. Genes Dev. 1996;10:3129\u20133140.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "8985182"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Joyner AL. Engrailed, Wnt, and Pax genes regulate midbrain-hindbrain development. Trends Genet. 1996;12:15\u201320.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "8741855"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Juul SE, Yachnis AT, Rojiani AM, Christensen RD. Immunohistochemical localization of erythropoietin and its receptor in the developing human brain. Pediatr Dev Pathol. 1999;2:148\u2013158.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9949221"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Koos BJ, Power GG. Predict fetal brain PO2 during hypoxaemia and anemia in sheep. J Dev Physiol. 1987;9:517\u2013526.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "3443723"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Lendahl U, Zimmerman LB, McKay RD. CNS stem cells express a new class of intermediate filament protein. Cell. 1990;60:585\u2013595.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "1689217"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Liu KJ, Hoopes PJ, Rolett EL, Beerle BJ, Azzawi A, Goda F, Dunn JF, Swartz HM. Effect of anesthesia on cerebral tissue oxygen and cardiopulmonary parameters in rats. Adv Exp Med Biol. 1997;411:33\u201339.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9269409"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Masuda S, Nagao M, Takahata K, Konishi Y, Gallyas F, Jr, Tabira T, Sasaki R. Functional erythropoietin receptors of cells with neural characteristics: comparison with receptor properties of erythroid cells. J Biol Chem. 1993;268:11208\u201311216.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7684373"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Max SR, Bossio A, Iacovitti L. Co-expression of tyrosine hydroxylase and glutamic acid decarboxylase in dopamine differentiation factor-treated striatal neurons in culture. Dev Brain Res. 1996;91:140\u2013142.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "8821486"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Maxwell PH, Wiesener MS, Chang GW, Clifford CS, Vaux EC, Cockman ME, Wykoff CC, Pugh CW, Maher ER, Ratcliffe PJ. The tumour suppressor protein VHL targets hypoxia-inducible factors for oxygen-dependent proteolysis. Nature. 1999;399:271\u2013275.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10353251"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Mayer-Proschel M, Kalyani AJ, Mujtaba T, Rao MS. Isolation of lineage-restricted neuronal precursors from multipotent neuroepithelial stem cells. Neuron. 1997;19:773\u2013785.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9354325"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "McKay RD. Stem cells in the central nervous system. Science. 1997;276:66\u201371.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9082987"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Moreau E, Vilar J, Lelievre-Pegorier M, Merlet-Benichou C, Gilbert T. Regulation of c-ret expression by retinoic acid in rat metanephros: implication in nephron mass control. Am J Physiol. 1998;44:F938\u2013F945.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9843911"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Morrison SJ, Csete M, Groves AK, Melega W, Wold B, Anderson DJ. Culture in reduced levels of oxygen promotes clonogenic sympathoadrenal differentiation by isolated neural crest stem cells. J Neurosci. 2000;20:7370\u20137376.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "PMC6772795",
                                    "11007895"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Nurse CA, Vollmer C. Role of basic FGF and oxygen in control of proliferation, survival, and neuronal differentiation in carotid body chromaffin cells. Dev Biol. 1997;184:197\u2013206.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9133430"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Olanow CW, Tatton WG. Etiology and pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease. Annu Rev Neurosci. 1999;22:123\u2013144.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10202534"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Olanow CW, Kordower JH, Freeman TB. Fetal nigral transplantation as a therapy for Parkinson's disease. Trends Neurosci. 1996;19:102\u2013109.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9054056"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Panchision D, Hazel T, McKay R. Plasticity and stem cells in the vertebrate nervous system. Curr Opin Cell Biol. 1998;10:727\u2013733.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9914183"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Paulding WR, Czyzyk-Krzeska MF. Regulation of tyrosine hydroxylase mRNA stability by protein binding, pyrimidine-rich sequence in the 3\u2032 untranslated region. J Biol Chem. 1999;274:2532\u20132538.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9891025"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Quelle FW, Wang J, Feng J, Wang D, Cleveland JL, Ihle JN, Zambetti GP. Cytokine rescue of p53-dependent apoptosis and cell cycle arrest is mediated by distinct Jak kinase signaling pathways. Genes Dev. 1998;12:1099\u20131107.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "PMC316716",
                                    "9553040"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Sakanaka M, Wen TC, Matsuda S, Masuda S, Morishita E, Nagao M, Sasaki R. In vivo evidence that erythropoietin protects neurons from ischemic damage. Proc Natl Acad Sci USA. 1998;95:4635\u20134640.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "PMC22542",
                                    "9539790"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Saucedo-Cardenas O, Quintana-Hau JD, Le WD, Smidt MP, Cox JJ, De Mayo F, Burbach JP, Conneely OM. Nurr1 is essential for the induction of the dopaminergic phenotype and the survival of ventral mesencephalic late dopaminergic precursor neurons. Proc Natl Acad Sci USA. 1998;95:4013\u20134018.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "PMC19954",
                                    "9520484"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Scandurro AB, Beckman BS. Common proteins bind mRNAs encoding erythropoietin, tyrosine hydroxylase, and vascular endothelial growth factor. Biochem Biophys Res Commun. 1998;246:436\u2013440.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9610379"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Shamim H, Mahmood R, Logan C, Doherty P, Lumsden A, Mason I. Sequential roles for Fgf4, En1 and Fgf8 in specification and regionalisation of the midbrain. Development. 1999;126:945\u2013959.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9927596"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Silver I, Erecinska M. Oxygen and ion concentrations in normoxic and hypoxic brain cells. Adv Exp Med Biol. 1988;454:7\u201316.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9889871"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Simone HH, Saueressig H, Wurst W, Goulding MG, O'Leary DD. En-1 and En-2 control the fate of the dopaminergic neurons in the substantia nigra and ventral tegmentum. Eur J Neurosci. 1998;10:389\u2013399."
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Smidt MP, van Schaick HS, Lanctot C, Tremblay JJ, Cox JJ, van der Kleij AA, Wolterink G, Drouin J, Burbach JP. A homeodomain gene Ptx 3 has highly restricted brain expression in mesencephalic dopaminergic neurons. Proc Natl Acad Sci USA. 1997;94:13305\u201313310.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "PMC24304",
                                    "9371841"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Studer L, Psylla M, Buhler B, Evtouchenko L, Vouga CM, Leenders KL, Seiler RW, Spenger C. Non-invasive dopamine determination by reversed phase HPLC in the medium of free-floating roller tube cultures of rat fetal ventral mesencephalon. A tool to assess dopaminergic tissue prior to grafting. Brain Res Bull. 1996;41:143\u2013150.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "8886383"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Studer L, Tabar V, McKay R. Transplantation of expanded mesencephalic precursors leads to recovery in parkinsonian rats. Nat Neurosci. 1998;1:290\u2013295.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "10195162"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Tammela O, Song D, Olano M, Delivoria-Papadopoulos M, Wilson DF, Pastuszko A. Response of cortical oxygen and striatal extracellular dopamine to metabolic acidosis in newborn piglets. Adv Exp Med Biol. 1997;411:103\u2013111.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9269417"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Wang MA, Jin P, Bumcrot DA, Marigo V, McMahon AP, Wang EA, Woolf T, Pang K. Induction of dopaminergic neuron phenotype in the midbrain by Sonic hedgehog protein. Nat Med. 1995;1:1184\u20131188.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7584992"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Wurst W, Auerbach AB, Joyner AL. Multiple developmental defects in Engrailed-1 mutant mice: an early mid-hindbrain deletion and patterning defects in forelimbs and sternum. Development. 1994;120:2065\u20132075.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "7925010"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Yamada T, Placzek M, Tanaka H, Dodd J, Jessell TM. Control of cell pattern in the developing nervous system: polarizing activity of the floor plate and notochord. Cell. 1991;64:635\u2013647.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "1991324"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Ye W, Shimamura K, Rubenstein JL, Hynes MA, Rosenthal A. FGF and Shh signals control dopaminergic and serotonergic cell fate in the anterior neural plate. Cell. 1998;93:755\u2013766.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "9630220"
                                ]
                            },
                            {
                                "Citation": "Zaman K, Ryu H, Hall D, O'Donovan K, Lin KI, Miller MP, Marquis JC, Baraban JM, Semenza GL, Ratan RR. Protection from oxidative stress-induced apoptosis in cortical neuronal cultures by iron chelators is associated with enhanced DNA binding of hypoxia-inducible factor-1 and ATF-1/CREB and increased expression of glycolytic enzymes, p21 (waf1/cip1), and erythropoietin. J Neurosci. 1999;19:9821\u20139830.",
                                "ArticleIdList": [
                                    "PMC6782985",
                                    "10559391"
                                ]
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "History": [
                    {
                        "Year": "2000",
                        "Month": "9",
                        "Day": "29",
                        "Hour": "11",
                        "Minute": "0"
                    },
                    {
                        "Year": "2001",
                        "Month": "3",
                        "Day": "3",
                        "Hour": "10",
                        "Minute": "1"
                    },
                    {
                        "Year": "2000",
                        "Month": "9",
                        "Day": "29",
                        "Hour": "11",
                        "Minute": "0"
                    }
                ],
                "PublicationStatus": "ppublish",
                "ArticleIdList": [
                    "11007896",
                    "PMC6772777",
                    "10.1523/JNEUROSCI.20-19-07377.2000"
                ]
            }
        }
    ]
}